<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Analyst Mindset</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Analyst Mindset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2011 - 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3 - Environmental Clinical Trial</title>
      <link>/2017/06/27/episode-3-environmental-clinical-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/27/episode-3-environmental-clinical-trial/</guid>
      <description>Background In this video I&amp;rsquo;m looking at data from the Mouse Allergen and Asthma Intervention Trial (MAAIT). This study was recently published and was a 2-arm randomized trial whose goal was to determine the effect of an integrated pest management (IPM) intervention on asthma morbidity among mouse-sensitized and exposed asthmatic children and adolescents. The trial took place in Baltimore, MD and Boston, MA. Participants were mouse-sensitized and exposed asthmatic children and adolescents, 5-17 years of age, randomized to receive professionally-delivered IPM plus pest management education or education alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Wildfire Smoke Composition</title>
      <link>/2017/06/05/episode-2-wildfire-smoke-composition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/05/episode-2-wildfire-smoke-composition/</guid>
      <description>Background In this episode I&amp;rsquo;m analyzing particulate matter air pollution data generated by wildfire smoke, which is a topic a bit closer to my everyday life (as opposed to the previous episode). Here, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to look at how the chemical composition of PM air pollution changes when there are wildfires. Wildfires represent a specific source of PM air pollution (in addition other sources like traffic, power plants, etc.) and they are relatively infrequent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Analyzing Lengths of Not So Standard Deviations Episodes</title>
      <link>/2017/05/22/episode-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/22/episode-1/</guid>
      <description>Background In the first episode of Analyst Mindset I (more or less on a whim) decided to look at the lengths of each of the episodes of Not So Standard Deviations, a data science podcast I do with Hilary Parker.
Goal Examine the relationship between the length of each episode and time/episode number to see if there&amp;rsquo;s any trend in the episode lengths over time.
Video Watch the analysis</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>