<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analyst Mindset</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Analyst Mindset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2011 - 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2 - Wildfire Smoke Composition</title>
      <link>/2017/06/05/episode-2-wildfire-smoke-composition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/05/episode-2-wildfire-smoke-composition/</guid>
      <description>Background In this episode I&amp;rsquo;m analyzing particulate matter air pollution data generated by wildfire smoke, which is a topic a bit closer to my everyday life (as opposed to the previous episode). Here, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to look at how the chemical composition of PM air pollution changes when there are wildfires. Wildfires represent a specific source of PM air pollution (in addition other sources like traffic, power plants, etc.) and they are relatively infrequent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Analyzing Lengths of Not So Standard Deviations Episodes</title>
      <link>/2017/05/22/episode-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/22/episode-1/</guid>
      <description>Background In the first episode of Analyst Mindset I (more or less on a whim) decided to look at the lengths of each of the episodes of Not So Standard Deviations, a data science podcast I do with Hilary Parker.
Goal Examine the relationship between the length of each episode and time/episode number to see if there&amp;rsquo;s any trend in the episode lengths over time.
Video Watch the analysis</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Analyst Mindset is a series of videos depicting me (Roger Peng) analyzing data. I try to provide some commentary as I go to explain a little of what I&amp;rsquo;m doing and what I&amp;rsquo;m thinking. You can find a list of all the videos on YouTube.
Bio Roger D. Peng is a Professor of Biostatistics at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health. He is also a co-founder of the Johns Hopkins Data Science Specialization, the Simply Statistics blog where he writes about statistics for the general public, the Not So Standard Deviations podcast with Hilary Parker, and The Effort Report podcast with Elizabeth Matsui.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>